

NGUYỄN HOÀNG ANH KHOA

BACK-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Щ

12/02/1999



binlove9225@gmail.com



Lê Văn Lương, Tân Quy, Quân 7, Hồ Chí Minh



0916497870

SKILLS

HTML5 & CSS3

JAVASCRIPT

REACTJS & REACT NATIVE

ANGULAR

ASP.NET

ENTITY FRAMEWORK

JAVA

NODEJS

GIT

DEPLOYMENT (AMAZON INSTANCES CS2, WINDOW SERVER)

About me

Hello! I'm Khoa. I'm a simple in appearance and mind. I like the newness of everything and I'm curious about those things. I have 1 sentence to say about myself that is "Experience beta people", it's mean "People who like to experience beta", because beta version is the last version of anything (^.^). Maybe that's why I like code. When I fix a bug, my curiosity is stimulated to the max, so I feel enjoy this "bug-fix..." loop, although I feel angry from time to time. I bet every developer will have the same feeling as me. The above is a few things about myself with programmer career IT WOULD BE NICE IF I COULD MEET YOU.

In previous work places, beside coding and developing. I can also research more cool stuff about technology and come up with technology solution and if it's better than old stuff then it's totally approved . I am quite interested in new technologies so in the future I want to be a Solution Architect. But in the immediate future, I have to try to work experience below LOL. Finally, I hope your company will be a part of my life, hope I can grow more here.

Projects

◆ THANGO LIVESTREAMING (WEB + 11/2021 - Present SDK)

It's a website to live stream. We provide an entertainment platform and connection between anchor (streamer) and visitor (viewer). At the same time, we build a SDK for customers who have needs for livestreaming in their technology products

- Building & developing Web Client User
- Building & developing Api for Front-End (Mobile App / Web App)
- Database architecture
- Building & developing Web CMS to manage the system's functions

Technical: NodeJS, Socket.io, Agora SDK, ReactJS

CRITERIA TO FIND A JOB

Stable income

Attached to the company for a long period of time

Positive & creative working environment

Many advancement opportunities

LANGUAGES

VIÊT NAM

Ngôn ngữ chính thống

ENGLISH

Good reading and writing ability Communication skills are still improving and developing

CONTACT ME



◆ PAYMENT PORTAL

It's a CRM Website for bussiness user (BU) of FE Credit to handle ticket. At the same time, it helps to manage customer relationships – online

- Building & developing Web Client User
- Build Api Gateway to interact with Api CoreBanking
- Build System to save activity & transaction logs
- Database architecture
- Building & developing Api for Front-End (Mobile App / Web App)

Technical: PHP Laravel Lumen, ReactJS

◆ NINO APP - NINOAPP.VN

10/2019 - 10/2021

Nino is a software system that manages and connects schools with students' parents, especially the preschool education system. It's built on the desire to create a close relationship between the school and parents. At the same time, Nino helps the school better manage its operational structure as well as its student system.

- Building & developing Api for Front-End (Mobile App / Web App)
- Database architecture
- Building & developing Webmaster (CMS + CRM) to manage the system's functions

Technical: .NET Core 3.1, Angular 7, React Native

◆ VITGYM APP-VITGYM.COM

10/2019 - 10/2021

Fitness, Gym, Yoga room management software is a crm software system for customer relationship management - online customer care for Fitness, Gym, Yoga clubs.

- Building & developing Api for Front-End (Mobile App / Web App)
- Database architecture
- Building & developing Webmaster (CMS + CRM) to manage the system's functions

Technical: .NET Framework 4.7, AngularJS, ReactJS

◆ SHOP.MOBIFONE8.COM.VN

4/2020 - 7/2020

It's a website for users who using Mobifone network to use services, read news and promotions of Mobifone. At the same time, it helps to manage customer relationships - online customer care for owners.

- Design the front-end and do the HTML/CSS my self with design thinking about UI/UX
- Database architecture
- Building & developing Back-End Api for web
- Building & developing Web CMS to manage system functions.

Technical: .NET Core 2.1, Angular 7, ReactJS

◆ BITRAVEL.VN

1/2020 - 3/2020

Bi Travel – Specializes in organizing Tour Team Building for reputable and quality companies. Novel, creative and experiential scenarios such as Team Building Amazing Race, Team Building trekking.

- Design the front-end and do the HTML/CSS my self with design thinking about UI/UX
- Database architecture
- Build Back-End Api for web
- Building & developing Web CMS to manage system functions.

Technical: .NET Core 2.1, Angular 7, ReactJS



Work Experiences

THANGO TVN

11/2021 - present

Full Stack Developer

- Responsible for working on a range of projects (3 projects at a time), designing appealing websites and interacting on a daily basis with graphic designers, back-end developers, and business analyst.
- Developing and maintaining the front-end functionality of websites.
- Database architecture for company product projects
- Handling Api for Front-End (Mobile App / Web App)
- Ensure the system runs right & stably, well optimized for performace and the right features according to the business and can develop more easily
- Participating in discussions with clients to clarify what they want.

VUONGTHANH.VN

5/2019 - 10/2021

Back-End Developer

- Database architecture for company product projects
- Handling Api for Front-End (Mobile App / Web App)
- Ensure the system runs right & stably, well optimized for performace and the right features according to the business and can develop more easily
- Build Product for company:
- Web master CMS CRM (ReactJS, Angular)
- Program a server (ASP.NET Core, .NET Framework)
- Program a database (SQL Server)
- Cloud (Amazon EC2, Window Server)

Education

◆ FPT-APTECH COMPUTER EDUCATION 08/2017 - 08/2019 HCM

Aptech Certified Computer Professional (ACCP)

- Semester 1: Logic Building and Elementary Programming with C,Designing and Publishing Websites, BootStrap and Jquery, AngularJS,eProject Website Development (HTML5),Database Management (SQL Server), Social Engineering and User Awareness
- Semester 2: Markup Language and JSON, Application
 Development Fundamentals-I, Application Development
 Fundamentals-II, Project Java, Application Programming, Web
 Application Development using PHP, Introduction to Big Data
- Semester 3: Windows Forms Programming, Web Application Development, Enterprise Application Programming (.NET),eProject (.NET),Mobile Computing and Cloud Computing,Introduction to Ethical Hacking,Introduction to Cloud Computing, Working with Cloud Computing
- Semester 4: Securing Web Applications, Introduction to Web and Enterprise Applications, Web Component Development (Servlets-JSP), Project (Java EE), Architecting Applications for the Web (JSF Struts), Enterprise Application Development (EJB), Creating Services for the Web (Web Services Java), Developing Applications for Wireless Devices, Fundamentals of IoT, Introduction to Cyber Forensics

◆ NGUYEN TRAI HIGH SCHOOL

2014 - 2017

High School Graduation

Grade: Good Conduct: Good